https://towertechinc.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
MENUMENUHomeProducts
Our Cooling Tower
TTXL Cooling TowerTTXR Cooling TowerRental Cooling TowerCooling Tower AccessoriesAftermarket ServiceTemporary Cooling Tower SolutionsConcrete Cooling TowersProduct Registration
Gallery
Medical Facilities GalleryUniversities GalleryPrison GalleryHotel GalleryGSA GalleryDistrict Energy Plant GalleryData Center GalleryChemical Plant GalleryManufacturing Plant GalleryGas Plant Gallery
Parts & ServiceAbout
Who We AreWhat We DoWhy Tower TechHistory of Tower TechCalculate Your SavingsReviewsFAQ'sGroup Policy
News & EventsContactProduct Registration
Privacy Policy
The Web site www.TowerTechInc.com is produced, owned and sponsored by Tower Tech, Inc., located in Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, U.S.A. Various types of information are collected from our Web site. The following provides details on how the information is collected and used.
Tower Tech collects two types of information: (1) Personal information; and (2) Non-personally identifiable information. Personal information may include names and addresses that are submitted when you request our literature or other services.
Non-personally identifiable information may include the type of browser being used by you (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, etc.), the type of operating system being used by you (e.g., Microsoft Windows, Macintosh, etc.), and the domain name of your Internet Service Provider (e.g., MSN, EarthLink, Cox Communications, etc.).
How We Use Collected Information
Tower Tech may use submitted information to fill requests for literature, provide follow-up sales information, make promotional offers, and supply requested services.
Tower Tech uses non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our Web site and to enable us to personalize the user’s Internet experience. The information we collect may be summarized into reports for the purposes of analyzing site usage. We may share non-personally identifiable information with pre-screened third parties for marketing or promotional purposes.
Tower Tech restricts access to collected information and requires that it only be used as required for the purposes of fulfilling the services offered by us.
We do not sell or otherwise distribute information to third parties except as previously described.
Cookies
Tower Tech uses “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that is written to your hard drive for recordkeeping purposes. This file is accessed, for example, to determine previously established viewing preferences. Cookies are not used to gain personal information that is not specifically supplied by the user.
The configuration of most browsers is initially set to accept cookies. Browsers can be set to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are sent. However, if you prevent the use of cookies the design functionality of our Web site may be impaired and the quality of your experience on our Web site will be lessened.
Third Party Links
Tower Tech may provide links to third party sites for the purpose of enhancing the viewing experience, for crediting sources, for providing access to needed browser plug-ins, or for other purposes. Third party sites may have different privacy policies and methodologies for protecting collected information. Viewers of those sites should be aware of this difference and read available privacy statements.
Usage Agreement
Your use of our Web site signifies your express agreement to the terms and conditions contained in this Privacy Statement. Tower Tech reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Questions or comments about our Privacy Policy should be directed to Info@TowerTechInc.com.
Let's Get Started!
Name*Email*
Phone*Message*CAPTCHANameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms.
Translate »
